/*
This software is Copyright ©️ 2020 The University of Southern California. All Rights Reserved. 
Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software and its documentation for educational, research and non-profit purposes, without fee, and without a written agreement is hereby granted, provided that the above copyright notice and subject to the full license file found in the root of this software deliverable. Permission to make commercial use of this software may be obtained by contacting:  USC Stevens Center for Innovation University of Southern California 1150 S. Olive Street, Suite 2300, Los Angeles, CA 90115, USA Email: accounting@stevens.usc.edu

The full terms of this copyright and license should always be found in the root directory of this software deliverable as "license.txt" and if these terms are not found with this software, please contact the USC Stevens Center for the full license.
*/
export const feedback = {
  userQuestions: {
    edges: [
      {
        cursor: "NjI5MDY0NGFkZDg3MzhkMjY5MmZiMjcw",
        node: {
          _id: "6290644add8738d2692fb270",
          question: "What is your name?",
          confidence: 1,
          classifierAnswerType: "EXACT",
          feedback: "NEUTRAL",
          updatedAt: "2022-05-27T05:40:26.675Z",
          createdAt: "2022-05-27T05:40:26.675Z",
          mentor: {
            _id: "60bad2ab733e6a54b909a351",
            name: "Aaron Shiel Version 1",
          },
          classifierAnswer: {
            _id: "6282c47949d92cf48c6b8a62",
            transcript: "My name is Aaron Shell.",
            question: {
              _id: "60c7b69407dd702a7c3c5963",
              question: "What is your name?",
            },
          },
          graderAnswer: null,
        },
      },
      {
        cursor: "NjI5MDYzZWE1OTQ5YTkwMDA5NDU3MDFk",
        node: {
          _id: "629063ea5949a9000945701d",
          question: "How old are you now?",
          confidence: 1,
          classifierAnswerType: "EXACT",
          feedback: "NEUTRAL",
          updatedAt: "2022-05-27T05:38:50.687Z",
          createdAt: "2022-05-27T05:38:50.687Z",
          mentor: {
            _id: "60bad2ab733e6a54b909a351",
            name: "Aaron Shiel Version 1",
          },
          classifierAnswer: {
            _id: "6282c47949d92cf48c6b8a81",
            transcript: "I am 25 years old.",
            question: {
              _id: "60c7b69407dd70415d3c5965",
              question: "How old are you now?",
            },
          },
          graderAnswer: null,
        },
      },
      {
        cursor: "NjI4ZDExYjA4ZGJlYzJhN2ZhNTBiYzc5",
        node: {
          _id: "628d11b08dbec2a7fa50bc79",
          question: "hey",
          confidence: -0.06329902941118393,
          classifierAnswerType: "CLASSIFIER",
          feedback: "NEUTRAL",
          updatedAt: "2022-05-24T17:11:12.384Z",
          createdAt: "2022-05-24T17:11:12.384Z",
          mentor: {
            _id: "6184d14c068d43dc6822a721",
            name: "Dr. Jennifer Trevitt",
          },
          classifierAnswer: {
            _id: "624d26315db8d6f2124df837",
            transcript: "My name is Dr. Jennifer Trevitt.",
            question: {
              _id: "60c7b69407dd702a7c3c5963",
              question: "What is your name?",
            },
          },
          graderAnswer: null,
        },
      },
      {
        cursor: "NjI4ZDExYTM4ZGJlYzIzMzhhNTBiYzc2",
        node: {
          _id: "628d11a38dbec2338a50bc76",
          question: "Do you have a nickname?",
          confidence: 1,
          classifierAnswerType: "EXACT",
          feedback: "NEUTRAL",
          updatedAt: "2022-05-24T17:10:59.177Z",
          createdAt: "2022-05-24T17:10:59.177Z",
          mentor: {
            _id: "6184d14c068d43dc6822a721",
            name: "Dr. Jennifer Trevitt",
          },
          classifierAnswer: {
            _id: "624d263b5db8d6f2124dfe9e",
            transcript:
              "I do. Actually, my family calls me Jenny, and they've called me that ever since I was a kid. And it's it's funny because there have been a few people in my adult life who, upon meeting me, just decided to call me Jenny. And it always just makes me feel not bad, but just interesting, because, really, the only other people in the world who call me that are people who I grew up with in my family.",
            question: {
              _id: "60d8d4069fcf35131d545612",
              question: "Do you have a nickname?",
            },
          },
          graderAnswer: null,
        },
      },
      {
        cursor: "NjI4NmM5YWU2MDcxOWFlMTBkZmQ3MGI3",
        node: {
          _id: "6286c9ae60719ae10dfd70b7",
          question: "Tell me about your family growing up.",
          confidence: 1,
          classifierAnswerType: "EXACT",
          feedback: "GOOD",
          updatedAt: "2022-05-19T22:50:39.530Z",
          createdAt: "2022-05-19T22:50:22.560Z",
          mentor: {
            _id: "60bad2ab733e6a54b909a351",
            name: "Aaron Shiel Version 1",
          },
          classifierAnswer: {
            _id: "6282c47949d92cf48c6b8a9c",
            transcript:
              "Growing up, it's kind of funny to say growing up was a lot of fun. I guess the better thing to say is when I was growing up it was a lot of fun with my family. I mean I grew up in Michigan until I was 12 with all of my, you know, immediate family and then I moved to California where I only had my close family after that, like my mom and my brother and sister, but before moving, Yeah, we would have thanksgiving dinner together all the time. Pretty much every holiday you can think of. We would get together for all holidays and outside of holiday season. Maybe we would always get together once a month to eat and just hang out. It was a lot of fun from hanging out with cousins.",
            question: {
              _id: "60c7b69407dd7007eb3c5968",
              question: "Tell me about your family growing up.",
            },
          },
          graderAnswer: null,
        },
      },
      {
        cursor: "NjI4NmM5YWU2MDcxOWFlMTBkZmQ3MGI4",
        node: {
          _id: "6286c9ae60719ae10dfd70b8",
          question: "New graded question",
          confidence: 0.4,
          classifierAnswerType: "OFF TOPIC",
          feedback: "NEUTRAL",
          updatedAt: "2022-05-19T22:50:39.530Z",
          createdAt: "2022-05-19T22:50:22.560Z",
          mentor: {
            _id: "60bad2ab733e6a54b909a351",
            name: "Aaron Shiel Version 1",
          },
          classifierAnswer: {
            _id: "A1_1_1",
            question: {
              _id: "A1_1_1",
            },
          },
          graderAnswer: {
            _id: "A1_1_1",
            question: {
              _id: "A1_1_1",
            },
          },
        },
      },
      {
        cursor: "NjI4NmM5YWU2MDcxOWFlMTBkZmQ3MGI5",
        node: {
          _id: "6286c9ae60719ae10dfd70b9",
          question: "New graded question",
          confidence: 0.4,
          classifierAnswerType: "OFF TOPIC",
          feedback: "NEUTRAL",
          updatedAt: "2022-05-19T22:50:39.530Z",
          createdAt: "2022-05-19T22:50:22.560Z",
          mentor: {
            _id: "60bad2ab733e6a54b909a351",
            name: "Aaron Shiel Version 1",
          },
          classifierAnswer: {
            _id: "A5_1_1",
            question: {
              _id: "A5_1_1",
            },
          },
          graderAnswer: {
            _id: "A5_1_1",
            question: {
              _id: "A5_1_1",
            },
          },
        },
      },
    ],
    pageInfo: {
      startCursor: null,
      endCursor: "eyIkb2lkIjoiNjI4MDcxYWIyYmFlNTkzYzY0NTA4OThjIn0",
      hasPreviousPage: false,
      hasNextPage: true,
    },
  },
};
